tetongravity.com 2019-05-07

# Teton Gravity Research | Action Sports - Ski, Snowboard, Bike, Movies

Date of last revision: May 4, 2015 

Teton Gravity Research, LLC (" **TGR** ", " **we** ", " **us** ", or " **our** ") takes the private nature of your information very seriously. This policy regarding our privacy practices (the " **Privacy Policy** ") describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit and use tetongravity.com (the " **Site** ") and/or TGR's other domains, products, advertising products, services, and/or content, including our iOS and Android mobile applications (collectively with the Site, the " **Services** "). When you use the Services, you also consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy; please read it carefully. 

##  **Our Policy**

Through the Site, we and our Service Provider may provide you with access to varied user-generated and other content and interactive and informational resources (collectively, “Services”). This Privacy Policy sets forth our policies with respect to information including personally identifiable data (“Personal Data”) and other information that is collected from you when using the Site. Unless otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, this policy shall be deemed to apply to us and all references to “we”, “us” and/or “our” shall include our Service Provider. 

## Information We Collect

When you interact with us through the Site, we may collect Personal Data and other information from you, as further described below: 

###  **Personal Data That You Provide Through the Site**

**Information we receive and how it is used** : We collect Personal Data from you when you voluntarily choose to provide such information such as when you, including: 

**Your information** is the information that’s required when you sign up for the site, as well as information you choose to share. 

**Registration information:** When you sign up for a TGR account, you are required to provide information such as your name, email address and sport.In some cases, you may be able to register using other information such as your TGR account. 

**Information you choose to share:** Your information also includes information you choose to share on TGR, such as when you post an update, upload a photo, comment on a friend’s story, contact us with inquiries, respond to one of our surveys, register for access to the Services or use certain Services. It also includes the information you choose when you take an action, such as when you add your favorite resort, like a Page or a website, add a place to your story, or indicate what activities you like. 

Wherever we collect Personal Data we make an effort to provide a link to this Privacy Policy. By voluntarily providing us with Personal Data, you are consenting to our use of it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data to this Site, you acknowledge and agree that such Personal Data may be transferred from your current location to our or our Service Provider’s offices and servers. 

Your name, profile pictures, cover photos, sports, username and User ID are treated just like information you choose to make public. 

###  **Public Information**

**Information that is always publicly available**

The types of information listed below are always publicly available, and they are treated just like information you decided to make public: 

  * **Name:** This helps your friends and family find you. If you are uncomfortable sharing your real name, you can always [_delete_](https://www.facebook.com/help/contact.php?show_form=delete_account) your account.
  * **Profile Pictures and Cover Photos:** These help your friends and family recognize you. If you are uncomfortable making any of these photos public, you can always delete them. Unless you delete them, when you add a new profile picture or cover photo, the previous photo will remain public in your profile picture or cover photo album. 
  * **Gender:** This allows us to refer to you properly. 
  * **Username and User ID** : These allow you to give out a custom link to your Profile Page and help make TGR Platform possible. 

**Usernames and User IDs**

Usernames and User IDs are the same thing – a way to identify you on TGR. A User ID is a string of numbers and a username generally is some variation of your name. With your username, you get a custom link that you can give out to people or post on external websites. 

If someone has your Username or User ID, they can use it to access information about you through the tetongravity.com website. For example, if someone has your Username, they can type tetongravity.com/Username into their browser and see your public information as well as anything else you've let them see. 

**How we use the information we receive**

We use the information we receive about you in connection with the services and features we provide to you and other users like your friends, our partners, the advertisers that purchase ads on the site, developers, applications, and websites you use. For example, in addition to helping people see and find things that you do and share, we may use the information we receive about you: 

  * as part of our efforts to keep TGR products, services and integrations safe and secure; 
  * to protect TGR's or others' rights or property; 
  * to provide you with location features and services, like telling you and your friends when something is going on nearby; 
  * to measure or understand the effectiveness of ads you and others see, including to deliver relevant ads to you; 
  * to make suggestions to you and other users on TGR, such as: suggesting that your friend like the same sports or activities 
  * for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research and service improvement. 

Granting us permission to use your information not only allows us to provide TGR as it exists today, but it also allows us to provide you with innovative features and services we develop in the future that use the information we receive about you in new ways. 

While you are allowing us to use the information we receive about you, you always own all of your information. Your trust is important to us, which is why we don't share information we receive about you with others unless we have: 

  * received your permission;
  * given you notice, such as by telling you about it in this policy; or 
  * removed your name and any other personally identifying information from it. 

Of course, for information others share about you, they control how it is shared. 

We store data for as long as it is necessary to provide products and services to you and others, including those described above. Typically, information associated with your account will be kept until your account is deleted. For certain categories of data, we may also tell you about specific data retention practices. 

We may enable access to public information that has been shared through our services. 

We may allow service providers to access information so they can help us provide services. 

**Non-Identifiable Data  **

When you utilize the Site, we may receive certain personally non-identifiable information about your use of the Site. Such information, which is collected passively using various technologies, cannot presently be used to specifically identify you. We may store such information ourselves or it may be included in databases owned and maintained by our affiliates, agents or service providers. We may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to the Site, the number of visitors to each page of the Site, and the domain names of our visitors' Internet service providers. It is important to note that no Personal Data is available or used in this process. 

In operating this Site, we may use cookies. A cookie is a piece of information that the computer or computers that host our Site give to your browser when you access the Site. Our cookies help provide additional functionality to the Site and help us analyze Site usage more accurately. For instance, our Site may set a cookie on your browser that keeps you from needing to remember and then enter a password more than once during a visit to the site. On most web browsers, you will find a “help” section on the toolbar. Please refer to this section for information on how to receive notification when you are receiving a new cookie and how to turn cookies off. We recommend that you leave cookies turned on because they allow you to take advantage of some of the Site’s features. 

**Aggregated Personal Data**

In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Services, we may conduct research on our end user’s demographics, interests and behavior based on the Personal Data and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and we may share this aggregated data with our affiliates, agents and business partners. This aggregate information does not identify you personally.We may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes. 

**Our Use of Your Personal Data and Other Information**

  * We will send you information about new Sweepstakes, rewards, upcoming events, and other news about products and services offered by Teton Gravity Research and our Marketing Partners
  * By participating in any contests or sweepstakes sponsored by Teton Gravity Research or third party marketing partner each contestant consents to receive promotional newsletters from Teton Gravity Research. You may opt-out of these newsletters by following instructions below.

**Choice/Opt-Out**

(a) You may opt-out of receiving promotional electronic messages from us by following the instructions in those messages. If you opt-out, we may still send you non-promotional electronic messages (as permitted by law) and postal mail, such as emails and postal mail about your accounts or our ongoing business relations. You may also send requests about changes to your information by emailing support@tetongravity.com. 

(b) To opt-out of our further sharing of your personal information with the Registration Partners, Marketing Partners and/or Sweepstakes Partners, you may contact us by emailing or writing to us at the address listed below. To opt-out of further receiving marketing from Marketing Partners and/or Sweepstakes Partners, you must do so directly with that Marketing Partners and/or Sweepstakes Partners. 

We will use the Personal Data you provide in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data for a certain reason, we may use the Personal Data in connection with the reason for which it was provided.For instance, if you contact us by e-mail, we will use the Personal Data you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem. Also, if you provide Personal Data in order to obtain access to the Services, we will use your Personal Data to provide access to such services and to monitor your use of such services. We may also use your Personal Data and other personally non-identifiable information collected through the Site to help us improve the content and functionality of the Site, to better understand our users and to improve the Services. We may use this information to contact you in the future to tell you about services we believe will be of interest to you. 

## Our Disclosure of Your Personal Data and Other Information

There are certain circumstances in which we may share your Personal Data with certain third parties without further notice to you, including as set forth below: 

**Business Transfers:** As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets.In the event of a sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event relating to all or a portion of our business, assets or this Site, Personal Data may be part of the transferred assets. 

**Service Providers, Agents and Related Third Parties:** We sometimes hire other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples include mailing information, maintaining databases and processing payments. When we employ another company to perform a function of this nature, we may need to provide them with access to certain Personal Data. However, we only provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function. 

**Legal Requirements:** We may also disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation, (ii) protect and defend our rights or property, (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Site or the public, or (iv) protect against legal liability. 

##  **Your Choices**

You can use the Site without providing any Personal Data, however, you may not be able to use certain Services. 

##  **Exclusions**

This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to us through this Site or to through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Site, such as bulletin boards (collectively, “Public Areas”), any ideas for new products or modifications to existing services, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, “Unsolicited Information”), including all User Content as that term is defined in our Terms of Use. All such Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and we shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such Unsolicited Information to others without limitation or attribution.Please also note that any Personal Data or other information you provide to be displayed in your publicly available online profile will be displayed for others to see and thus will not be subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy. We cannot and will not be responsible for what third parties do with any Personal Data or other information that you choose to make publicly available. As such, we advise that you exercise great care in determining what information you choose to make publicly available through this Site. 

### Children

We do not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 13. If you are under thirteen, please do not submit any Personal Data through the Site. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children to never provider Personal Data on this Site without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Data to us through this Site, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases. 

### Links to Other Websites

This Privacy Policy applies only to the Site. The Site may frame or contain references or links to other websites not operated or controlled by us or our Service Provider (the “Third Party Sites”). The policies and procedures we described here do not apply to the Third Party Sites. The links from the Site do not imply our review or endorsement of the Third Party Sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy policies. 

### Security

Your Account Information is protected by a password for your privacy and security.We take reasonable steps to protect the Personal Data provided via the Site from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction.However, no Internet or e-mail transmission is ever fully secure or error free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from the Site may not be secure. Therefore, you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail. Please keep this in mind when disclosing any Personal Data to us Provider via the Internet. 

## Shop

### RISK OF LOSS

All items purchased from TGR are made pursuant to a shipment contract. This means that the risk of loss and title for such items pass to you upon our delivery to the carrier. 

### RETURNS, REFUNDS AND TITLE

TGR does not take title to returned items until the item arrives at our fulfillment center. At our discretion, a refund may be issued without requiring a return. In this situation, Amazon does not take title to the refunded item. For more information about our returns and refunds, please see our Returns Center 

### PRODUCT DESCRIPTIONS

TGR attempts to be as accurate as possible. However, TGR does not warrant that product descriptions or other content of any TGR Service is accurate, complete, reliable, current, or error-free. If a product offered by TGR itself is not as described, your sole remedy is to return it in unused condition. 

### PRICING

Except where noted otherwise, the List Price or Suggested Price displayed for products on any TGR represents the full retail price listed on the product itself, suggested by the manufacturer or supplier, or estimated in accordance with standard industry practice; or the estimated retail value for a comparably featured item offered elsewhere. The List Price or Suggested Price is a comparative price estimate and may or may not represent the prevailing price in every area on any particular day. For certain items that are offered as a set, the List Price or Suggested Price may represent "open-stock" prices, which means the aggregate of the manufacturer's estimated or suggested retail price for each of the items included in the set. 

With respect to items sold by TGR, we cannot confirm the price of an item until you order. Despite our best efforts, a small number of the items in our catalog may be mispriced. If the correct price of an item sold by TGR is higher than our stated price, we will, at our discretion, either contact you for instructions before shipping or cancel your order and notify you of such cancellation. Other merchants may follow different policies in the event of a mispriced item. 

We generally do not charge your credit card until after your order has entered the shipping process or, for digital products, until we make the digital product available to you. 

### **COLORS**

We made every effort to display as accurately as possible the colors of our products that appear at the Website. As the actual colors you see depend on your computer monitor, however, we cannot guarantee that your monitor's display of any color will be accurate. 

**What Information You Can Access**

If you are a registered user, you can access most information associated with your Account by logging into the Services and checking your Account Profile page. Registered and unregistered users can access and delete cookies through their web browser settings. 

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

The Site may change from time to time. As a result, at times it may be necessary for us to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Accordingly, we reserve the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice. Please review this policy periodically, and especially before you provide any Personal Data.This Privacy Policy was last updated on the date indicated above. Your continued use of the Site after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy. 

### Access to Information and Contacting Us

Through the Site, we provide you with access to update your profile and revise Personal Data previously submitted to the Site. You may contact us in the event you have questions about Service this Privacy Policy or our information practices. You may contact us at the contact details set forth above in our Terms of Use.
